A Guide to the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Executive Journals 1991
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Secretary of the Commonwealth, Executive Journals, 1991
Library of Virginia
34442
9 cubic feet
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Restorations of rights, pardons granted, extradition renditions and requisitions are restricted (public access and photoduplication) to those with written authorization from the Secretary of the Commonwealth. Guide to the collection available in Archives Manuscript Room.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth on May 25, 1993.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth has evolved from early colonial times when there existed a Secretary of the Colony. Thomas Nelson held the position of the first Secretary of Virginia in 1776. Early Secretaries were elected by the public. An Act of the General Assembly in 1920 changed the election to a joint vote of the General Assembly. In a 1930 Act the duties of the Secretary were redefined with the Secretary of the Commonwealth serving as the ex officio secretary of the Governor, as custodian of many official State records, and as keeper of the Greater and Lesser Seals of the Commonwealth. The office of the Secretary has gradually acquired other functions, such as: service of out-of-state civil process; appointment and regulation of notaries public; and registration and oversight of lobbyists. The Office became a gubernatorial appointment subsequent to a 1958 Act of the Assembly. The Secretary of the Commonwealth is under the jurisdiction of the Governor's Office.
The Secretary is appointed by the Governor for a term of four years. Currently the Secretary of the Commonwealth is responsible for gubernatorial appointments, clemency and restoration of civil rights requests and extraditions. Additional activities include: serving as ex officio Secretary to the Governor; serving as keeper of the seals of the Commonwealth; compiling and publishing the annual Blue Book; commissioning and regulating notary publics, including the publication of a Notary Handbook and conduct of disciplinary hearings; promulgating the lobbying disclosure requirements, registration of lobbyists, and recording of lobbying reports; servicing the civil process of out-of-state defendants and other parties; and authenticating and certifying the records of the courts and of any state agency. Governor-elect James Gilmore appointed Anne P. Petera, chairwoman of the State Alcoholic Beverage Control Board in the Allen Administration, secretary. Petera served until the end of Gilmore's administration in January 2002.
Scope and Content
The Executive Journals of the Secretary of the Commonwealth contain the permanent record of the Governor's appointments, executive orders and memorandums, commissions, notaries, pardons, writs of election, restoration of rights, renditions and requisitions. This accession consists of the records of the second year of Governor Lawrence D. Wilder's administration (January-December, 1991).
Arrangement
The records for Governor Wilder are arranged by date then type of record, alphabetically.
Contents List
- List of Contents, 1991 January-September (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Appointments, 1991 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Appointments, 1991 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Appointments, 1991 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 January 3 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Notaries, 1991 January 4 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Notaries, 1991 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Notaries, 1991 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Appointments, 1991 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Appointments, 1991 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Appointments, 1991 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 February 8 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Notaries, 1991 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Notaries, 1991 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Notaries, 1991 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Notaries, 1991 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Appointments, 1991 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Appointments, 1991 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Appointments, 1991 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Appointments, 1991 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Appointments, 1991 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Appointments, 1991 March 18 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Appointments, 1991 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Appointments, 1991 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Notaries, 1991 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Notaries, 1991 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Notaries, 1991 March 20 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Notaries, 1991 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Orders, 1991 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Proclamations, 1991 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Proclamations, 1991 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Proclamations, 1991 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Appointments, 1991 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 April 25 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Notaries, 1991 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Notaries, 1991 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Notaries, 1991 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Notaries, 1991 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Orders, 1991 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Writs of Election, 1991 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Appointments, 1991 May 9 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Notaries, 1991 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Notaries, 1991 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Notaries, 1991 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Notaries, 1991 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Notaries, 1991 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Orders, 1991 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Orders, 1991 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Orders, 1991 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Orders, 1991 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- Proclamations, 1991 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Appointments, 1991 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Appointments, 1991 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 June 13 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 June 21 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Notaries, 1991 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 116)
- Notaries, 1991 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Notaries, 1991 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Notaries, 1991 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Orders, 1991 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Appointments, 1991 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Appointments, 1991 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Appointments, 1991 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Appointments, 1991 July 22 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Appointments, 1991 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Appointments, 1991 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 126)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 127)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 3 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 130)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 11 (Box 1, Folder 131)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 15 (Box 1, Folder 133)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 16 (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 18 (Box 1, Folder 135)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 136)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 23 (Box 1, Folder 137)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 138)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 140)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 141)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 30 (Box 1, Folder 142)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 143)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 144)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 146)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 147)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 July 22 (Box 1, Folder 148)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 149)
- Notaries, 1991 July 3 (Box 1, Folder 150)
- Notaries, 1991 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 151)
- Notaries, 1991 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 152)
- Notaries, 1991 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 153)
- Proclamations, 1991 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 154)
- Writs of Election, 1991 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 155)
- Appointments, 1991 August 5 (Box 1, Folder 156)
- Appointments, 1991 August 9 (Box 1, Folder 157)
- Appointments, 1991 August 19 (Box 1, Folder 158)
- Appointments, 1991 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 159)
- Appointments, 1991 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 160)
- Appointments, 1991 August 27 (Box 1, Folder 161)
- Appointments, 1991 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 162)
- Appointments, 1991 August 30 (Box 1, Folder 163)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 1 (Box 1, Folder 164)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 5 (Box 1, Folder 165)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 6 (Box 1, Folder 166)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 167)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 168)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 9 (Box 1, Folder 169)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 13 (Box 1, Folder 170)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 171)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 16 (Box 1, Folder 172)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 19 (Box 1, Folder 173)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 174)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 175)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 176)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 177)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 27 (Box 1, Folder 178)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 28 (Box 1, Folder 179)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 180)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 August 30 (Box 1, Folder 181)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 August 19 (Box 1, Folder 182)
- Notaries, 1991 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 183)
- Notaries, 1991 August 9 (Box 1, Folder 184)
- Orders, 1991 August 30 (Box 1, Folder 185)
- Appointments, 1991 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 186)
- Appointments, 1991 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 187)
- Appointments, 1991 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 188)
- Appointments, 1991 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 189)
- Appointments, 1991 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 190)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 3 (Box 1, Folder 191)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 192)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 5 (Box 1, Folder 193)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 194)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 195)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 196)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 197)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 198)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 199)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 200)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 16 (Box 1, Folder 201)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 17 (Box 1, Folder 202)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 203)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 Septmeber 19 (Box 1, Folder 204)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 20 (Box 1, Folder 205)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 21 (Box 1, Folder 206)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 207)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 208)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 25 (Box 1, Folder 209)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 210)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 211)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 212)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 213)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 214)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 215)
- Notaries, 1991 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 216)
- Notaries, 1991 September 20 (Box 1, Folder 217)
- Orders, 1991 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 218)
- List of Contents, 1991 October-December (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Appointments, 1991 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Appointments, 1991 October 21 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Appointments, 1991 October 26 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Appointments, 1991 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 7 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 11 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 18 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 21 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 29 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 30 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 October 21 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 October 30 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Memorandums, 1991 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Notaries, 1991 October 4 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Notaries, 1991 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Notaries, 1991 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Orders, 1991 October 14 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Orders, 1991 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Orders, 1991 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Proclamations, 1991 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Proclamations, 1991 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Appointments, 1991 November 1 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Appointments, 1991 November 6 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Appointments, 1991 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Appointments, 1991 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Appointments, 1991 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Appointments, 1991 November 26 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 1 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 4 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 5 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 6 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 12 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 17 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 19 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 20 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 21 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 22 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 25 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 26 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 27 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 November 1 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 November 20 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 November 26 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Notaries, 1991 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Notaries, 1991 November 25 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Proclamations, 1991 November 4 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Proclamations, 1991 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Proclamations, 1991 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Proclamations, 1991 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Appointments, 1991 December 3 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Appointments, 1991 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Appointments, 1991 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Appointments, 1991 December 12 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Appointments, 1991 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Appointments, 1991 December 17 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Appointments, 1991 December 20 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Appointments, 1991 December 23 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Appointments, 1991 December 30 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 2 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 3 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 5 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 12 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 17 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 18 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 23 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 24 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 26 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 30 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1991 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 December 2 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 December 30 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1991 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Notaries, 1991 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Notaries, 1991 December 23 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1991 February 8 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1991 March 14 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1991 March 15 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1991 March 18 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1991 April 2 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1991 August 5 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1991 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1991 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1991 November 20 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 23 (Box 2, Folder 119)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 28 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 123)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 January 31 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 1 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 8 (Box 2, Folder 126)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 11 (Box 2, Folder 127)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 21 (Box 2, Folder 128)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 22 (Box 2, Folder 129)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 25 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 13 (Box 2, Folder 132)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 15 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 18 (Box 2, Folder 134)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 22 (Box 2, Folder 136)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 March 29 (Box 2, Folder 137)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 April 16 (Box 2, Folder 138)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 April 30 (Box 2, Folder 140)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 144)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 May 23 (Box 2, Folder 145)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 May 24 (Box 2, Folder 146)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 147)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 148)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1991 June 6 (Box 2, Folder 149)